

# SUPHANUT CHANDEE

FRONT END DEVELOPER PBANGKOK, THAILAND 092-624-4589

#### · DETAILS ·

Bangkok Thailand 092-624-4589 suphanut.work@gmail.com

### · SKILLS ·

Work in a Team
Time Management

_	Time management
	Communication
	HTML
	CSS
	TypeScript
	JavaScript
	Yarn
	React
	React Native
	NextJs
	Git
	GitHub
	7.00

GitLab

Ant Design

React Router

Supabase

· LANGUAGES ·

Thai

English

HOBBIES

Read light novels.

Listen to music.

# PROFILE

I am a **Web and Mobile Application developer**, primarily working with TypeScript and JavaScript frameworks like Next.js, React, and React Native. While Ant Design is my go-to UI library, I also adapt to specific needs by using other libraries, such as Leaflet and FullCalendar.

I enjoy exploring **new approaches**, and I believe that every experience, no matter how small, adds value and will benefit me in the future.

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

# Front end Developer at Witsawa Corporation Co.,Ltd, Bangkok

May 2023 - Present

- Developed and Optimized web applications using React and Next with JavaScript and TypeScript
- Developed and Optimized LINE-LIFF applications using React and TypeScript.
- Developed and Optimized applications using React Native with JavaScript and TypeScript,

#### \*\* INTERNSHIPS

# QA/Tester at Witsawa Corporation Co.,Ltd, Bangkok

April 2022 - June 2022

- Test 4 projects (Thai Survive Line-liff, Thai Survive Distribution Center, Thai Survive Super Admin, Classwin).
- Use Cypress, Cucumber, Chrome Developer Tools for Auto Test.
- · Use Google Docs, Sheet, Figma for Project Test and QA

## EDUCATION

## Bachelor's degree, Kasetsart University, Bangkok

July 2019 — March 2023

# Faculty of Engineering Department of Computer Engineering

Gained valuable experience from my senior project in the following areas:

- · Developed the frontend using React.ts.
- · Implemented backend functionalities with Node.js.
- · Managed the database using MongoDB.
- Worked with hardware components, utilizing ESP32 and ADXL345, programmed by AduinoIDE with C.
- · Integrated real-time notifications using LINE Notify.

# High school diploma, Satit Kaset Kamphaeng Saen Campus, Nakhon Pathom

April 2016 - March 2019

· SMP (Science Mathematics Program)